Metric
Let X be a non-empty set
Def: A function p:XxX→R satisgying the following conditions:
(1)	p(x,y)=0 iff x=y
(2)	p(x,y)<=p(x,z)+p(y,z)    (the triangle inequality)
for all x,y,z in X is called a metric on X.
Def: The set X along with a metric p is called a metric space and is denoted by (X,p).
The elements of (X,p) are called points. The number p(x,y) is called the distance between the points x and y.
THEOREM: A metric p:XxX→R has the following properties:
(1)	p(x,y)>=0 and p(x,y)=0 iff x=y
(2)	p(x,y)=p(y,x)   (symmetry)
(3)	P(x,y)<=p(x,z)+p(z,y) for all x,y,z in X
EX: 1. Any set can be endowed with the following metric:
P(x,y)=1 if x<>y and 0 if x=y we refer to this type of metric as a discrete metric.
2. The function p:RxR→[0,inf) p(x,y)=|x-y| metric on R called the Euclidean metric.
3. The fucn p:CxC→[0,inf) p(z1,z2)=|z1-z2| is the Euclidean metric on C.
4. The func p1:R^nxR^n→[0,inf) p1(x,y)=sum(i=1 to n){|xi-yi|} where x=(x1,....,xn) and y=(y1,....,yn) is the Minkovski metric on R^n. Also known as Manhattan distance, taxi-cab metric or city block distance, this metric is often used in integrated circuits where wires only run parallel to the x or y axis.
EX: the func p2:R^nxR^n→[0,inf) p2(x,y)=rad{sum(i=1 to n){(xi-yi)^2} where x=(x1,....,xn) and y=(y1,....,yn) is the Euclidean metric on R^n.
EX: the func pinf:R^nxR^n→[0,inf) pinf(x,y)=max{|xi-yi|}, where where x=(x1,....,xn) and y=(y1,....,yn) is the Chebyshev metric on R^n.
