Let (X,p) be a metric space.Consider the set
X^N:=xxxx....xxxx....={f|f:N→x}
Def: An element f from X^n is called a sequence. Using the notation f(n)=xn, we denote the sequence (x0,x1,.....,xn,...) by using the symbol (xn).
The element xn is called the nth term of the sequence.
Def: A sequence (xn) is said to be convergent if there exists x in X s.t. for every eps>0 the number of xn terms lying outside the ball B(x,eps) is finite.
The point x is called the limit of the series (xn) and we use the notation lim(n to inf)xn=x or xn tinde la x.
Def: A sequence (xn) in the metric space (X,p) is said to be fundamental or Cauchy sequence iff, for all eps>0 ther exists reps in N s.t. p(xn,xm)<eps for all n,m in N, n,m>reps.(dist dintre termeni devine tot mai mica)
Remark: Any convergent sequence is fundamental.
Def: A metric space (X,p) is said to be complete iff any Cauchy sequence from X converges to a point from X.(spatiu care contine limitele sirului lui)
EX: The space Q with the Euclidean metric p(x,y)=|x-y| is not a complete space.
((1+1/n)^n) in Q^N is fundamental, however (1+1/n)^n tinde la e not in Q
Remark: In order to prove that a sequence (xn) is fundamental it is sufficient to find a sequence of real positive numbers (epsn) convergent to zero s.t. p(xn+p,xn)<=epsn for all n,p in N.

