Let a sebseR. Consider a function (fn) of real functions defined on A and f:A-->R.
Def: A functional sequence (fn) is convergent to f on A denoted by fn-->f if lim(n to inf)fn(x)=f(x) for all x in A.
Def: A functional sequence is said to be uniformly convergent to f on A, denoted by fn-->(U)f if for all eps>0 there exists reps s.t. |fn(x)-f(x)|<eps for all n in N, n>reps for all x in A.
THEOREM: If the functions fn:[a,b]-->R are continuous and if fn-->(U)f then f is continuous on the closed interval [a,b].
THEOREM: Let (fn) be a uniformly convergent sequence of continuous functions on [a,b]. Then the following equality holds: lim(n to inf){int(a-b){fn(x0dx}}=int(a-b){lim(n to inf){fn(x)dx}}
By virtue of the previous theorem we deduce
COROLLARY: A uniformly convergent series of continuous functions on a closed interval [a,b] can be integrated termwise.
THEOREM: Let (fn) be a sequence of functions in C’[a,b]. If (fn) converges to a function f, and the sequence of the derivatives (f’n) is uniformly convergent to a function g, then there exists f’ and f’=g.
		lim(n to inf)f’n=(lim(n to inf)fn)’
THEOREM(Weierstrass): If suman is a convergent series of numbers, and the functional series of real functions (fn) satisfies the inequalities: |fn(x)|<=an for all x in A, all n in N, then the functional series sumfn is uniformly and absolutely convergent on A.

   




