Let (an) be a sequence of complex numbers and z0 in C.
Def: The series sum(n>=0){an(z-z0)^n} is called a power series in powers of (z-z0) and coefficients (an).
Making thye substitution x=z-z0 we obtain a power series in powers of x.
THEOREM(Abel): If a power series sum{an*x^n} converges at a point x0<>0, then it converges uniformly and absolutely in every closed disc. D(barat)(0,r)={x in C||x|<=r}
Proof: Let x in D. Since the series sum(an*x0^n) is convergent, then there exists a number M s.t. |an*x0^n|<=M for all n in N.
We have: sum|an*x^n|=sum|an*x0^n|*|x/x0|^n<=M*sum|r/x0|^n for all x in D. By Wierstrass’s theorem, we deduce that the series suman*x^n is unifoemly and absolutely convergent on the domain D.
We use the notation lim(barat)an=sup{the limit points set of an}
EX: limsup(-1)^n=1;limsup(1-)^n/n=0;limsup(1+(-1)^n)*n=inf
Def: The element R=1/limsuprad ord n{|an|} in [0,inf] on condition 1/0=inf an 1/inf=0 is called the radius of convergence of the series suman*x^n.
The set D(0,R)={x in C| |x|<R} is called the disc of convergence of the series.
THEOREM: Let R be the radius of convergence of the series suman*x^n, then
-	if R=0, then suman*x^n is convergent only at the point x=0
-	if 0<R<inf then suman*x^n is convergent in the set D(0,R) (and divergent outside the disc)
-	if R=inf, then suman*x^n is convergent in C
Remark: When the limit lim(n to inf)|an/an+1| exists, then the radius of convergence R of suman*x^n can be computed by R=lim(n to inf)|an/an+1|
THEOREM(Abel-Tauber): If 0<R<inf is the radius of convergence of a series suman*x^n and if the series of numbers sumanR^n is convergent, then lim(x to R,x<R)suman*x^n=suman*R^n
Remark: Since the series suman*x^n, sumn*an*x^(n-1) and suman/n+18x^(n+1) have the same radius of convergence, any power series can be formally differentiated and integrated term-by-term in the domain of convergence.
Functions of complex variable which can be expanded into convergent power series are called analytic functions. They are situated as a branch of advanced mathematics called The Theory of Analytic Functions or The Theory of Functions of Complex Variables.
EX: e^z:=1+z/1!+z^2/2!+z^3/3!+....
cosz:=1-z^2/2!+z^4/4!-.....   sinz:=z-z^3/3!+z^5/5!-.....
For real z=x these definitions lead to the well-known real functions e^x,cosx,sinx. It is obvious that for any complex number z we have: e^iz=cosz+isinz; cosz=(e^iz+e^(-iz))/2; sinz=(e^iz-e^(-iz))/2i  Euler’s formulas


   




