Def: In a topological space, a set is said to be closed iff its complement is open.
We denote the family of all closed sets in the topologoical space (X,T) by F(dm)
	F(dm)={F|C(F) in T}={C(G)|G in T}
Remark: The notations of closed set and open set are dual notions. They are neither exclusive (same sets can be simultaneously open and closed) nor exhaustive (some sets are neither open nor closed).
EX: 1. In the case of the minimal topology {X,void}    F0={X,void}
2. T1=P(X)   F1=P(X)
3. T={void,{1},{1,2}}   F2={{1,2},{2},void}



