(X,T)-top. sp. and x in X
A set V subseq X is called a neighborhood of X if there exists G in T s.t. x in G subseq V
The neighborhood of a point x in X is denoted by Vx and is called the system of neighborhoods of X.
EX: 1. In case of T0={void,X} we have Vx={X} for all x in X
2. In case of T1=P(X) Vx={V| (V subseq X) ˄ (x in V)}
3. T={void,{1},{1,2}}   V1={{1},{1,2}}    V2={{1,2}}

The following theorem gives a characterisation of the open sets.
!!!THEOREM: In a topological space a set is open iff it is neighborhood for all its points.




