Def: A family T of subsets of a non-empty set X satisfying the properties:
	T1:the union of any collection of sets from T belongs to T
	T2:the intersection of any 2 sets from T belongs to T
	T3:X and void belong to T
Is called a topology on T.
The familiy
EX: T={void; {1}; {3}; {1,3}; {1,2,3}} is a topology on X={1,2,3}

Def: The pair (X,T) where X is a set and T is a topology on X is called a topological space. The elements of X are called points of the topological space. The elements of T are called open sets of the topological space.

The axioms of the first definition can be stated as follows:
	(T1) The union of a collection of open sets is an open set.
	(T2) The intersection of 2 open sets is an open set.
	(T3) X and void are open sets.

-	T0={void,X} the minimal topology on X
-	T1=P(x) the maximal topology on X
-	Tn={G,void|G subseq R ˄ (for every x in G, there exists I-open interval s.t. x in IsubseqG)} the natural topology of the real axis

