(X,T)-top. sp. and x in X
Def: A point x is said to be an interior point of A subseq X if there exists a neighborhood V in Vx s.t. V subseq A.
The set of all interior points of A is called the interior of A and denoted by int(A). Therefore, 
		X in int(A) iff the exists V in Vx , V subseq A
!!!THEOREM: int(A) is the largest open set contained in A, i.e. int(A)=U G (Asubseq invers G in T)
EX: In case of T={void,{1},{1,2}}    int({1})={1}    int({2})=void
In case of the natural topology we have int([0,1])=(0,1)  int([0,1))=(0,1)  int({0})=void;
THEOREM: In a topological space, a set M is open iff M=int(M).
Proof: necessity: we suppose that M is an open set of the top. sp. (X,T) and we have to prove that M=int(M)
U G subseq M  (M subseq invers G in T)   trivial (1)
M subseq U G (M subseq invers G in T)   (2)
(M subseq invers M in T, hence M is a term of the union) From (1), (2): M=U G=int(M) (M subseq invers G in T)
Sufficiency:suppose that M=int(M). Since int(M) is open (as a union of open sets), M is open.
Remark: From the previous theorem we deduce that a set G is open iff G subseq int(G)
THEOREM: The interior operator, int:P(X)→T has the following properties:
1.	Int(A) subseq A
2.	Int(A∩B)=int(A) ∩ int(B)
3.	Int(int(A))=int(A)
4.	Int(X)=X
1.	The inclusion int(A) subseq A can be obtained from the relation: int(A)=U G subseq A (A subseq invers G in T)
2.	It is obvious that A subseq B then int(A) subseq int(B)
3.	From A ∩ B subseq A then int(A∩B) subseq int(A)
From A ∩ B subseq B then int(A∩B) subseq int(B)
It follows that int(A∩B) subseq int(A) ∩ int(B)    (3)
From int(A) subseq A       int(B) subseq B
We obtain int(A) ∩ int(B) subseq A∩B
Therefore int(int(A) ∩ int(B)) subseq int(A∩B)
Thet is int(A) ∩ int(B) sebseq int(A∩B)    (4)
(3),(4) we obtain int(A) ∩ int(B) subset int(A∩B)
	3. using the fact that int(A) in T we obtain int(int(A))=int(A)
      4.  X is an open set, therefore X=int(X)
Properties 1 and 4 are specific for the interior operator.





