Def: A point x in the top sp (X,T) is called a limit point or an accumulation point of a given set A subseq X if there is at least one point in A, other than X, in each neighborhood of the point X.
The set of all limit points of A is called the derived set of A: A’
              x in A’ iff   x in ad(A\{x})
The previous equality implies the inclusion: A’ subseq ad(A)
Def: The point of A\A’ is said to be an isolated point of A.
Def: A set is said to be discrete if each of its points is isolated. (N,Z)
EX: In case of the natural topology of the real axis we have:
[0,1)’=[0,1]
{1,1/2,1/3,....,1/n,....|n in N*}’={0}
In case of the maximal topology T=P(X), for all A subseq X  A’=void
In general there is no inclusion relation between the sets A’ and A”. One knows that int(A)=C(ad(C(A)))
We also tried to express the derivation operator using a formula that involves the other usual topological operators. A negative answer to this peoblem is presented in the following theorem.
THEOREM: The derivation operator cannot be written in terms of a finite number of closure, intersection and complement operators. (M.Ivan,1996)








