Def: The trigonometric series a0/2+sum(n>=1){ancosnX+bnsinnX}, where the coefficients an and bn are given by an=1/pi*int(-pi to pi){f(x)*cosnxdx} (n>=0) and bn=1/pi*int(-pi to pi){f(x)*sinnxdx} (n>=1) is called the Fourier series of the function f and we write f(x)~a0/2+ sum(n>=1){ancosnX+bnsinnX}.
The Fourier series of a function f can be written also in complex form as: f(x)~sum(n=-inf to inf){cn*e^inx}, where the coefficients cn are given by cn=1/2pi*int(-pi to pi){f(t)*e^(-int)dt}.

Remark: The Fourier series associated with the function f, can be convergent or divergent. In some cases it converges to f.

Remark: If f is an even function, then its Fourier coefficients are given by: an=2/pi*int(0 to pi){fx*cosnxdx} (n>=0) and bn=0 (n>=1) if f is an odd function an=0 (n>=0) and bn=2/pi*int(0 to pi){f(x)*sinnxdx} (n>=1)
Remark: There exist trigonometric series which are not Fourier series. For example sum(n>=1)sinnx/radn is not a Fourier series(it does not satosfy the Parseval equality)
Def: A function posessing a finite number of points of discontinuity of the first kind and no points of discontinuity of the second kind is said to be piecewise continuous.
Def: A function is said to be piecewise smooth if both f and f’ are piecewise continuous.

THEOREM(Dirichlet): If a function f is piecewise smooth, then its Fourier series converges to 
f(x-0)+f(x+0)/2 for all x in R


Remark:If a function f in C^1(R) is periodic, then its Fourier series converges unifromly to f.
Remark: The Fourier series associated to any integrable function f:[a,b]-->R is
a0/2+sum(n=1 to inf)(ancos2npi/(b-a)x+bnsin2npi/(b-a)x)
where an=2/b-aint(a la b)f(x)cos2npi/(b-a)xdx  n in N
bn=2/b-aint(a la b)f(x)sin2npi/(b-a)xdx   n in N*

THEOREM(Parseval): If a function f:[-pi,pi]-->R and the square of its modulus are integrable, then its Fourier coefficients satisfy the equality:
a0^2/2+sum(n>=1)(an^2+bn^2)=1/piint(-pi la pi)f^2(x0dx




   




