Let E subseq R^n, f:E-->R and x=(x1,...,xn) be a point in EintE’
Def: The partial derivative of a function f at a point x, with respect to xk, is defined as the limit 
parf/parxk(x):=f’xk(x)=lim(t-->xk){[f(x1,...,xk-1,t,xk+1,...,xn)-f(x1,...,xn)]/t-xk} provided the lim exists
If a function posesses a derivative with respect to xk at each point in EintE’, then the function x|-->f’xk(x) is deonted by parf/parxk or f’xk and is called the partial derivative of f with respect to xk. 
Another notation(the good one) is f(0,0,..,0,1,0,...,0) where “1” is placed at the kth position.
EX: let f:R^2-->R s.t. f(x,y)=x^2*y+e^xy
Then f^(1,0)(x,y)=parf/parx(x,y)=2xy+ye^xy
f^(0,1)(x,y)=parf/pary(x,y)=x^2+x*e^xy
Remark: The existance of partial derivatives of a function at a point DOES NOT imply the continuity of the function at that point.
The higher order partial derivatives of a function f are defined by induction:
Par^2f/parxpary=(def)par/parx(parf/pary)
We write: f’’yx=(f’y)x=(def)par^2f/parxpary
In general, the mixed partial derivatives f’’xy and f’’yx are not equal to eachother.
As it will be shown later, in many important cases, the operations of successive partial differentiation can be interchanged withouth affecting the final result.
Let a subseq R^2
THEOREM(Schwarz): If f:A-->r posesses continuous mixed partial derivatives f’’xy and f’’yx in a neighborhood of a point (x0,y0) in A, then these derivatives are equal to eachother at that point: f’’xy(x0,y0)=f’’yx(x0,y0).


