THEOREM: In any metric space we can define the following topology:
T={void,G subseq X| for all x in G, there exists r>0 s.t. B(x,r) subseq G}
The topology defined in the previous theorem is called the topology indused by the metric p.
Remark: In the topology induced by the metric p the open balls are open sets.
Indeed, for all y in B(x,r) we have B(y,r-p(x,y)) subseq B(x,r) that is B(x,r) in T.


