Let (X,p) and (Y,tau) be 2 metric spaces. The following definition is deduced directly from the definition of the continuity on a topological space.
Def: A mapping f:(X,p)→(Y,o) is said to be continuous at a point x in X if for any eps>0, there exists delta(x,eps)>0 s.t. for all x’ in X   p(x,x’)<delta(x,eps) then o(f(x),f(x’))<eps.
Def: A mapping f:(X,p)→(Y,o) is said to be uniformly continuous if for every eps>0 there exists delta(eps)>0 s.t. for every x, x’ in X p(x,x’)<delta(eps) then o(f(x),f(x’))<eps.
