Let (X,Tx) and (Y,Ty) be two topological spaces
Def: A function f:(X,Tx)→(Y,Ty) is said to be continuous of a point x in X if for each neighborhood U in Vf(x) there exists a neighborhood V in Vx s.t. f(V) subseq U.
THEOREM: A function f:(X,Tx)→(Y,Ty) is continuous on X iff the inverse image under f of every open(closed) set in (Y,Ty) is an open(closed) set in (X,Tx).
Remark: In general, the image of an open(closed) set under a continuous function is not an open(closed) set.
THEOREM(Weierstrass): If f:(X,Tx)→R is continuous and A subseq X is a compact set, then f attains its greatest and least values on A. (compact set=in the natural topology of R^n a set is compact iff it is closed+bounded).
Remark: The requierment of the last theorem that A be compact is essential.

