A,B-sets   I-non empty index set {Ai|i € I} be a collection of sets
(Bn)n € N be a sequence of sets. We define the following set operations.

-	The union of A and B
A U B =(def) {x| x € A or x € B}  “A cup B”
-	The intersection of A and B
A ∩ B =(def) {x| (x € A)˄(x € B)}  “A cap B”
If A ∩ B=void we say that A and B are disjoint, otherwise A and B intersect.
-	The difference between A and B
A \ B =(def) {x| (x € A) ˄ (x not in B)}  “A minus B”
In order to denote the difference A\B, also called the complement of B relative to A, we use the notation CA(B) or C(B).
-	The symmetric difference of A and B
AΔB =(def) (A\B) U (B\A)
-	The Cartesian product of A and B
A x B =(def) {(a,b)| (a in A)˄(b in B)}  “A times B”
-	The union of a collection of sets
UAi = (def) {x| there exists i, i in I ˄ x in Ai}
-	The intersection of a collection of sets
∩Ai =(def) {x|for every i (i in I → x in Ai)}

The power set of a set A is the collection of all subsets of A: P(A)=(def) {X|X subseq A}

The limit inferior of a sequence of sets: liminf(Bn)=(def) U∩Bn  (k from 0 to inf,n from k to inf)

The limit superior of a sequence of sets: limsup(Bn)=(def) ∩UBn
