THEOREM: If M is a set and A={x|x € M ˄ x not in x} then A not in M.
Proof: suppose that A € M. By the definition of A, the relation A € A implies A not in A. Similarly A not in A implies A € A. So the relation A € M implies A € A iff A not in A which is impossible. Hence, the assumption A € M is false.
CORROLARY: The class of all sets is not a set.
Suppose that “the class of all sets” is a set and denote it by M. Then the set A defined in the previous theorem does not belong to M. It follows that M cannot be “the set of all sets”. Therefore, we say “the class of all sets”.


