Let F(dm) be the class of all sets. We consider a relation ‘~’(equivalent) where
			A~B iff(def) there exists f:A→B, a bijection
	In what follows, we assign, to a given set A, a symbol called the cardinal number of A. This symbol is the same for all sets which are equivalent with respect to the relation ‘~’ and is denoted by card(A) or |A|. If the set A is finite, then card(A) can be identified with the number of its elements.
EX: |{0;1;2}|=3   card(void)=0, card(N)=card(Z)=card(Q)=aleph zero(N0)   card(R)=card(C)=aleph(N)
The sets with cardinal number aleph zero are said to be countable.

The most famous problem in set theory is the continuum hypothesis proposed by Cantor: N subs X subs R (no cardinal lies between aleph0 and aleph). He was unable to prove this as a theorem of set theory. Godel and Cohen demonstrated the independence of the continuum hypothesis by showing that the axioms of the set theory would remain consistent, assuming they were initially consistent.


