Let (xn)-sequence of complex numbers
Consider the sequence (Sn): Sn=x0+x1+.....+xn   (n in N)
The pair ((xn),(Sn)) is called a series and is denoted by ∑xn or ∑(n>=0)xn or ∑(n=0 to inf)xn
The number Sn is called the nth partial sum of the series.
The number xn is the general term of the series.
The sum sum(n=0 to inf)xn of the series sumxn if formally defined by: 
sum(n=0 to inf)xn:=lim(n to inf){sum(k=0 to n)xk=lim(n to inf)Sn
The series sumxn is said to be convergent iff the sequence (Sn) is convergent.
If the sequence (Sn) has no limt, or the limit is infinite, then the series is said to be divergent.
To denote that the series sumxn and sum yn are simultaneously convergent or divergent, we use the notation sumxn ~~sumyn
A series of positive terms is reffered to as a positive series. The sequence of the partial sums of a positive series is increasing. Hence, it has a limit and we deduce: A positive series is convergent iff the sequence of the partial sums is bounded. 
Def: The series sumxn is said to be absolutely convergent if the series sum|xn| is convergent.
EX: sum(n=1 to inf){1/2^n}=1 is conv
sum(n=1 to inf){1/n}=inf is div
sum(n>=0){(-1)^n} is div
sum(n>=0){sin n} is div
sum(n>=1){(-1)^n/n is conv but not absol conv (-ln2)

Let sum(n=0 to inf)an and sum(n=0 to inf)bn be two series of real numbers
Def: The series sum(n=0 to inf)sum(k=0 to n){akb(n-k)} is called the Cauchy product of the two series
The Cauchy product of 2 convergent series is not necessarilly a convergent series.
THEOREM: (Mertens) If the series sum(n=0 to inf)an is absolutely convergent and sum(n=0 to inf)bn is convergent, then their Cauchy product is a convergent series, and 
sum(n=0 to inf)sum(k=0 to n){akb(n-k)}=sum(n=0 to inf)ansum(n=0 to inf)bn
